Battle Book Start!
That's how you prove a thing exists.
This one and this one.
Here you go.
Can you stop taking pictures for a second?
Uh, just...
This is an office, so please don't be too much of a fan of that kind of thing.
Oh, I'm a staff member. I'm sorry.
Oh, you're a staff member.
I didn't know. I'm sorry. Excuse me.
He's already gone before.
Okay.
What's the video about?
It's a wand tube.
One-tube! Let's get this right.
Hello, one-tube viewers. My name is Ririka Ozawa.
Please follow me on Instagram and Twitter.
I love YouTube!
Suddenly, commingle.
What are you in the middle of?
I'm playing a game right now.
Please don't look at me when I'm playing a game.
Oh, I'm not looking.
This is the complicated face version.
I'm choosing Asha. I'll do my best.
The chi-chi face championship.
No, wait a minute. We're playing the chiisana face championship.
This one, this one.
That's a bad smile.
They're doing something.
What if we win?
What if I win?
Awkward face... the winner of the new test.
I'll send you some awkward food.
Awkward food?
Awkward food from the manager.
What is awkward food?
All kinds of awkwardness.
What kind of awkwardness?
They give it to me and draw me a picture or something.
Oh, that's nice.
I don't know.
Oh, I'm not interested anymore.
I was just thinking of something awkward.
You were thinking of something awkward?
I was.
Then think about it.
That's a tough one.
I'll think about it.
I'm sorry.
It won't come out.
It makes me feel bad.
Yeah, yeah.
I'll be natural.
There's some kind of surprised face, but I don't remember.
Batubu.
We're shooting Arthur from Berryz today on Battube.
It's early. The evening sun is shining now.
I don't know what to do.
I don't know what's the most confusing thing about my picture.
Big size Arthur photo shoot.
Big size Arthur.
It's early.
Good morning.
It's been a while.
Souvenir.
Jichiro!
Yay!
I heard that there are no bad people who give you Jichiro.
Good people are givers.
Good people are also good evaluators.
I heard that.
Thank you, Jichiro.
Thank you, Mr. Jichiro.
A person named Jiichiro gave me this.
My mom bought me strawberries for Christmas the other day.
They are so cute!
But my mom also bought me mikan the other day.
My mom also bought strawberries and mikan that day.
My mom was going to say she likes strawberries, oranges, and grapes.
Well, is that okay?
What color do you like?
What color do you like for your mother's mother?
I knew Worcester was a good group.
They are so cute.
We're going to be shooting music videos again today, but it's going to be a little late.
Let's do our best. It was early in the morning.
I'll do my best.
I haven't seen you in a while.
Stop it.
It's embarrassing.
Don't give me that crap about your mom's strawberries.
Stop it already. I'm talking about my private life.
Snicker.
Laugh through your nose.
I'll do my best.
I'll do my best. Quick.
I'll do my best, but early.
I'll dance as hard as I can.I'll dance as hard as I can.
Good morning.
What day is it today?
Today is...
Oh, no, no, no, no, suddenly.
Let's see...
I'll do my best!
It's a music video.
Stray cats... what is it?
The Great War.
I'll do my best!
I'm wearing gloves.
Aah! The wind is coming!
Wind is cold!
Wind!
I'll do my best!
Shippo-yan's character
He looked like he was in a bad mood.
I'm sure he's not.
We were blessed with beautiful weather.
I'm so happy to see a big difference from the spring fireworks
I'm so happy to see a big difference.
A little more this way.
Oh, I went a little too far.
It's hard.
It's too hard.
I'm sorry.
It's a big place.
Thank you.
Let's sing a prayerful epilogue song.
For the days we've laughed, the days we've cried, the days we've cried, they've been taken from us
If the blue sky is deprived of one thing
There's also a great warmth.
Thank you.
Bye-bye!
Grow up healthy.
Grow up.
You're going to school.
I studied hard, so it's for my future.
Don't give up.
That's a lot of weight.
You should study.
The luster of the rock.
Heavy.
The costume this time.
The shoulders are pretty open.
It looks cold.
But it was so sunny today.
It's a good day to shoot a music video outside.
I am very happy.
I'm doing my best with the leakage ahead of time.
It's getting harder and harder to get on.
Shoo!
I can't hear the osomatsu sound, so please shake the sound from your head.
All right, let's get started!
Is it cold?
It's not cold. It's not cold, but it's burning.
It burns. Oh, I see. You should come.
I didn't think it would be this warm.
Even today you said it was like the coldest day.
That's great, Asta.
But it's been raining all day, so I'm a little fired up.
I'm working hard.
But I'm off for a while after this, so I'm going to bed.
I'm doing my best.
Filming in progress
I feel like the shooting is going really well today.
I'll do my best!
Thank you for watching!
The little kids.
Cute kids!
They are running!
I want to go back!
They're cute.
They sure are.
Little kids.
They're cute.
I'm doing my best.
Wasa-chan.
I know it's always tough shooting music videos, and I feel sorry for you.
But please tweet to tell her that she's doing a great job.
Everyone.
Hashtag Lilika the child.
Please.
That's all I have to say.
Yes, please.
Please do it.
All right, let's start!
Cut!
One more time!
OK!
Thank you!
I'm calling Ahorapi.
Let me put my hand like this...
Oh, this one!
Aho sososo...
Yes, cut!Yes, cut!
OK!
Thank you!
Reaction
Oh no!
I think I'll eat it first.
Aah! Aah! Aah! Aah! Aah! Aah!
A-ha-ha!
The Demon King! The Demon King!
Uh! Uh! Uh! Aah! Aah! Aah! Aah! Aah!
These chocolate cake-like triangles are absolutely delicious!
What's this? It's delicious, isn't it?
Ah! Fish!
I got so much of this!
I got so much fish!
It's like that. It's like cat food.
It's so cute! It's so cute!
I want some!
Excuse me, Sanmai, please.
Let's get started!
Okay, okay.
Okay, you can go a little faster.
Good, good, good.
Yes, cut.
Okay, ready, ready.
Okay, cut. Okay.
Thank you. Thank you.
Perfect.
It's cold.
Now, what, what?
Oh, there's snacks.
Am I in here?
What? Up here?
Can I eat it?
Ha! I'm like, "Can I eat it?
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
You can eat it!
I'm afraid the members will get mad at me and ask me to keep it a secret.
Ha-ha-ha!
They're gonna be so mad at me!
hahaha
Thank you for watching!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
What? Can I eat it?
You can eat it.
What? Can I eat it now?
Yes, yes.
Now it's time to eat up!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I'm going to have a blast!
Here we go!
Yay!
Yay! Yay!
Yay! Yay! Yay!
The group had more fun.
Okay, cut. Okay.
Maybe the camera's on top.
The group is all camera.
Yes, cut.
I'm telling the truth.
Look at the steam.
In junior high school, we had these yellowtail sapocon things, you know, the things you take off.
The one that you get.
Wow!
Can you see the steam? Can you see it?
Is it something?
There it is, it's not here. Bon appétit.
This is Miri.
Steam, steam, steam, see?
It's steam.
Can you see it? Can you see it?
I'm so happy.
Ready, ready.
Se-no-se, yes.
Okay, okay.
Okay, last one.
Se-no, yes.
OK!
Thank you very much.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you for watching.
Okay, I'll go.
You're going.
Ready, set, go!
Se-no!
Se-no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Se-no-yes!
Se-no-yes
Se-no!
Se-no! Yes! Oh, yes! Se-no! Yes!
Sey! Yes! Sey! Yes! Ready!
Yes, cut!
OK!
Okay! Oh, yeah!
Ready!
Yes! Yes!
Yes!Yes!
Special Lesney.
Oh, that's a very nice video.
Yes, cut!
OK.
Cut.
Yes, cut!
Perfect.
Yes, okay, everyone, play it!
Yes, good!
Cut! Cut!
Yes, cut!
OK!
Well, that's it, Nanase. Yes, all done!
Thank you very much!
I took all the all-ups!
It was fun! It's a little hot, but I think it will be a good music video!
Watch it everyone!
Thank you very much!
Thank you for your hard work!
Yay!
Thank you for today.
Thank you for your hard work.
It's looking good. I'm sure.
It was cold. It was cold, but
I got through it with power.
I got over it with power.
Yes, I did. I couldn't think of anything.
So, I will warm myself up and go to bed when I get back home.
That's right.
How many times do you want to replay one competitor's dance? I'm looking at it.
Oh, like that?
Yeah.
Three times is what I'm expecting.
It's getting better and better.
I'd like to see it 43 times.
43 times is good?
Maybe a few times with 430 mistakes.
No, let's be realistic.
Okay, 12 times is fine.
Have three people send me 12 times.
Oh, that's good.
Have them send it to me.
Send a lot of realism.
Send it to 43 people or watch it 43 times.
Um, see 430 times.
I worked hard today.
I did my best.
Bye-bye.
I studied hard, so it's for the future.
Don't give up!
It has a lot of weight.